<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubots | Blog</title>
    <description>Blog da Ubots</description>
    <link>ubots.com.br/blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="ubots.com.br/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 13:39:10 -0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 13:39:10 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chatbots para impulsionar as vendas no e-commerce</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;José, 24 anos, acaba de comprar um perfume no seu e-commerce favorito, ao final da compra, seleciona a opção de receber informações sobre a situação do pedido pelo Facebook Messenger. Dois dias depois ele recebe uma mensagem do Facebook Messenger, no seu celular, avisando que o seu pedido encontra-se com a transportadora e chegará em mais um dia. José agradece e aproveita para perguntar se a empresa possui uma colônia pós barba, o “atendente” responde que infelizmente não possui o produto em estoque, mas avisará assim que o produto estiver disponível.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;José agradece novamente e, ao final, fica sabendo que quem estava do outro lado da conversa não era um humano e sim um “chatbot”.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Há um tempo plataformas de mensagens como o Facebook Messenger, Skype e Telegram eram responsáveis, unicamente, por intermediar conversas entre usuários humanos. As recentes evoluções em Inteligência Artificial e a criação de plataformas em torno desses aplicativos são os principais combustíveis para a ascensão dos chatbots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Chatbots são softwares que utilizam inteligência artificial para conversar com pessoas através de aplicativos de mensagens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chatbots podem, por exemplo, disponibilizar produtos e serviços através de conversas e possuem potencial para ser o próximo grande passo na evolução das interações na internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Em abril de 2016 Mark Zuckerberg, o criador do Facebook, &lt;a href=&quot;http://olhardigital.uol.com.br/pro/noticia/facebook-lanca-plataforma-de-robos-para-o-messenger/57116&quot;&gt;anunciou a plataforma&lt;/a&gt; que possibilita que empresas criem seus próprios chatbots e softwares atrelados ao Facebook Messenger. Entre outras afirmações, Zuckerberg disse: “você deveria ser capaz de enviar uma mensagem para uma empresa da mesma forma que envia a um amigo” e ainda afirmou: “você nunca mais terá de ligar para um call center”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Em maio de 2016, logo após o lançamento, a plataforma do Messenger já contava com &lt;a href=&quot;http://g1.globo.com/tecnologia/noticia/2016/07/facebook-ja-tem-11-mil-robos-batendo-papo-no-messenger.html&quot;&gt;mais de 11 mil chatbots registrados&lt;/a&gt; e, desde então, vem sofrendo constantes evoluções para se tornar uma forma completa de interação entre as empresas e seus consumidores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;De acordo com o relatório da &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kpcb.com/internet-trends&quot;&gt;KBPC sobre tendências da internet&lt;/a&gt;, os aplicativos de mensagem já ultrapassaram as mídias sociais como método preferido de comunicação da Geração Y (geração das pessoas que nasceram após os anos 80).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As gigantes empresas americanas de tecnologia como Google, Microsoft, Apple, IBM e Facebook estão conduzindo grandes avanços nas áreas de inteligência artificial e computação cognitiva. Essas empresas estão produzindo novos produtos e tecnologias a cada dia, além de estarem, constantemente, realizando aquisições de empresas menores que possuem inovações relevantes na área.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outras empresas de diversos setores e portes já estão tirando proveito de todos esses avanços e utilizando chatbots no Messenger para melhorar a comunicação com  seus clientes. Como são os casos do Banco Original, Vivo, CNN por exemplo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Algumas empresas de e-commerce também estão atentas a essa nova oportunidade e já lançaram os seus chatbots, a americana &lt;a href=&quot;http://digiday.com/brands/two-months-1-800-flowers-facebook-bot-working&quot;&gt;1-800 flowers&lt;/a&gt; (venda de flores), a europeia &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.skyscanner.net/news/tools/skyscanner-facebook-messenger-bot/&quot;&gt;Skyscanner&lt;/a&gt; (um dos principais sites de pesquisa de viagens do mundo) e a Panvel Farmácias (maior rede do sul do país) são exemplos disso. Segundo Chris McCann, presidente da 1-800 Flowers, após apenas alguns meses, mais de 70% das compras feitas pelo chatbot foi de novos clientes. Já Éthel Ribas, uma das responsáveis pelo serviço de atendimento ao cliente da Panvel Farmácias, relata que, em menos de 3 meses, houve uma perceptível melhora na qualidade e, principalmente, na capacidade do atendimento sem aumentar os custos operacionais.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Segundo uma &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abcomm.org/pesquisa-atendimento-no-ecommerce.php&quot;&gt;recente pesquisa&lt;/a&gt; da Associação Brasileira de Comércio Eletrônico (ABCom) 73% dos consumidores preferem falar com a empresa por um chat. No entanto, apesar deste alto índice, menos da metade das lojas estão utilizando essa ferramenta e algumas delas ainda escondem essa informação ao invés de colocá-la em destaque.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As empresas de e-commerce devem se preparar para essa nova realidade e potencializar o atendimento aos clientes utilizando as plataformas de mensagens, especialmente o Facebook Messenger, como um novo canal automatizado e inteligente de SAC e vendas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Se a sua empresa utiliza o &lt;a href=&quot;http://e-commerce.vtex.com/10-motivos-para-escolher-a-plataforma-de-e-commerce-vtex&quot;&gt;sistema de e-commerce da VTEX&lt;/a&gt;, saiba que já pode contar com um chatbot no Facebook Messenger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Ubots, parceira da VTEX e desenvolvedora do chatbot da rede de Farmácias Panvel, desenvolveu uma plataforma de chatbots totalmente integrada ao sistema da VTEX e ao Facebook Messenger. Por meio dessa plataforma, o seu e-commerce possuirá um atendimento automatizado e inteligente alcançando seus clientes onde eles estão. Acompanhamento de status de pedidos, SAC, busca e vendas de produtos são apenas alguns exemplos das opções que você pode disponibilizar através dessa plataforma.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0200</pubDate>
        <link>ubots.com.br/blog/e-commerce/2017/01/04/chatbots-para-impulsionar-as-vendas-no-e-commerce.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">ubots.com.br/blog/e-commerce/2017/01/04/chatbots-para-impulsionar-as-vendas-no-e-commerce.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>e-commerce</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yeah, Mr. White! Yeah, science!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is glass grade. I mean, you got… Jesus, you got crystals in here 2 inches, 3 inches long. This is pure glass. You’re a damn artist! This is art, Mr. White! Yeah, that’s the thing, y’know? Your scumbag brother-in-law took my rainy day fund. Oh yeah. And tell that douche bag brother-in-law of yours to go towards the light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;this-is-an-h2&quot;&gt;This is an H2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took this vo-tech class in high school, woodworking. I took a lot of vo-tech classes, because it was just big jerk-off, but this one time I had this teacher by the name of… Mr… Mr. Pike. I guess he was like a Marine or something before he got old. He was hard hearing. My project for his class was to make this wooden box. You know, like a small, just like a… like a box, you know, to put stuff in. So I wanted to get the thing done as fast as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I figured I could cut classes for the rest of the semester and he couldn’t flunk me as long as I, you know, made the thing. So I finished it in a couple days. And it looked pretty lame, but it worked. You know, for putting in or whatnot. So when I showed it to Mr. Pike for my grade, he looked at it and said: ‘Is that the best you can do?’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;this-is-an-h3&quot;&gt;this is an h3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first I thought to myself ‘Hell yeah, bitch. Now give me a D and shut up so I can go blaze one with my boys.’ I don’t know. Maybe it was the way he said it, but… it was like he wasn’t exactly saying it sucked. He was just asking me honestly, ‘Is that all you got?’ And for some reason, I thought to myself: ‘Yeah, man, I can do better.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I started from scratch. I made another, then another. And by the end of the semester, by like box number five, I had built this thing. You should have seen it. It was insane. I mean, I built it out of Peruvian walnut with inlaid zebrawood. It was fitted with pegs, no screws, I sanded it for days, until it was smooth as glass. Then I rubbed all the wood with tung oil so it was rich and dark. It even smelled good. You know, you put nose in it and breathed in, it was… it was perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;code class=&quot;language-scss&quot;&gt;.hero-img {
    position: absolute;
    top: 0;
    left: 0;
    right: 0;
    bottom: 0;
    z-index: 1;
    background-position: center top;
    background-size: cover;
    &amp;amp;:after {
        position: absolute;
        content: '';
        width: 100%;
        height: 100%;
        background: rgba($primaryColor, 0.4);
    }
}&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What? Come on! Man, you’re smart. You made poison out of beans, yo. Look, we got, we got an entire lab right here. Alright? How about you pick some of these chemicals and mix up some rocket fuel? That way you could just send up a signal flare. Or you make some kind of robot to get us help, or a homing device, or build a new battery, or… wait. No. What if we just take some stuff off of the RV and build it into something completely different? You know, like a… Like a dune buggy. That way, we can just dune buggy or… What? Hey? What is it? What?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;this-is-an-h4&quot;&gt;this is an H4&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Four pounds… foooour pounds as if two pounds wasn’t bad enough. we’re talking two three hundred boxes of sinus pills there ain’t that many Smurfs in the world. So no sudo? So you do have a plan! Yeah, Mr. White! Yeah, science!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>ubots.com.br/blog/science/2015/08/08/yeah-mr-white-yeah-science.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">ubots.com.br/blog/science/2015/08/08/yeah-mr-white-yeah-science.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Science</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I handle the business operations</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Has your condition worsened? Your medical condition, has it grown worse? Is there a ringing in your ears? Are you seeing bright lights or hearing voices? No, clearly you are not. No rational person would do as you have done. Explain yourself. Are you asking me if I ordered the murder of a child? Where is Pinkman now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;this-is-an-h2&quot;&gt;This is an H2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I handle the business operations. With all due respect, Don Eladio. I didn’t sell it to them. I gave them samples. I gave them samples to give to you. To introduce you to our product. This product is the drug of the future. It’ll triple your profits. Perhaps quadruple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, you deal almost exclusively in cocaine. But the coca plant can’t grow in Mexico. You are no more than middlemen for the Colombians. They cut you a percentage for smuggling across the border. But the lion’s share of the profit goes to them, despite your assumption of all the risk. And you keep all the profits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;this-is-an-h3&quot;&gt;this is an h3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don Eladio, please. I didn’t sell anything. I apologize if you are offended by my method of obtaining this meeting. I merely took the initiative. I meant no insult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are done. Fired. Do not show your face at the laundry again. Stay away from Pinkman. Do not go near him. Ever. Are you listening to me? What do you say? For now, but he’ll come around. In the meantime there’s the matter of your brother-in-law. He is a problem you promised to resolve. You have failed. Now is left to me. To deal with him. If you try to interfere, this becomes a much simpler matter. I will kill your wife, I will kill your son, I will kill your infant daughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;code class=&quot;language-scss&quot;&gt;.about-img {
    margin-bottom: $pad;
    text-align: center;
    img {
        width: 140px;
        height: 140px;
        border: solid 5px $lightGrey;
        border-radius: 100%;
    }
}&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you know what’s happening upstairs? This is all a result of your former partner. Do you understand now? Do you see why this can’t continue? There will be an appropriate response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tyrus told me what’s happening - the sick child. I understand your preoccupation, but Jesse, I am running a business. I need you back at the lab to complete the cook. You can return when you’re done. It is, as you must know, in both of our best interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;this-is-an-h4&quot;&gt;this is an H4&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I… am very sorry. Is there anything I can do? I am on the board of this hospital. I can recommend doctors. Make sure he gets whatever he needs. The best treatment. How did that happen? This current batch is surely ruined now, correct? Stay with the boy. Tyrus will dump what’s there and clean the tanks. You will start a new batch when you are ready to return. Next week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>ubots.com.br/blog/business/2015/08/08/i-handle-the-business-operations.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">ubots.com.br/blog/business/2015/08/08/i-handle-the-business-operations.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>business</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Because I say so</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What am I eighth grade hall monitor? Current whereabouts? Let me tell you something, Mike. There are rules to this lawyer thing. Attorney client privilege, that’s a big one. That’s something I provide for you! &lt;!--more--&gt; If I give up Pinkman, then you’re gonna be asking, old Saul gives ‘em up pretty easy what’s to keep him from giving me up? You see, so then, where’s the trust?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;this-is-an-h2&quot;&gt;This is an H2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s your lucky day. Look around, kiddo - it’s all yours. You are now the owner of this fine establishment. Free? Oh ladies, cover your ears. No… not free. Look, hey… this is a squeaky clean, highly profitable (at least potentially), local institution. Look the bottom with favor by the chamber of commerce, better business bureau at three-hundred and twelve thousand dollars, it’s a steal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two words: nail, salon. It’s perfect for money laundering, it’s a high-volume, cash-preferred business with a discreet workforce. Nobody does mista-me-know-nothing better than Mrs. Mukjayaporn and her gals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;this-is-an-h3&quot;&gt;this is an h3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look, let’s start with some tough love, alright? Ready for this? Here it goes: you two suck at peddling meth. Period. Good! ‘Oh boo-hoo, I won’t cook meth anymore!’ You’re a crybaby! Who needs you?! Hey, I’m unplugging the website, so no more money laundering! How do you like that?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You want your criminal associate taken into police custody? We declare just enough so as to not arouse suspicion, so Walt’s one time winnings becomes seed money for an investment. If you’re committed enough, you can make any story work. I once told a woman I was Kevin Costner, and it worked because I believed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;code class=&quot;language-scss&quot;&gt;@mixin breakpoint($mq) {
    @if $mq == small {
        @media (min-width: 500px) {
            @content;
        }
    } @else if $mq == medium {
        @media (min-width: 720px) {
            @content;
        }
    }  @else if $mq == large {
        @media (min-width: 1200px) {
            @content;
        }
    }  
}&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello. Welcome. What a pleasure it is to have you. Just gonna call you Skyler if that’s okay. It’s a lovely name. It reminds me of the big, beautful sky. Walter always told me how lucky he was, prior to recent unfortunate events. Clearly his taste in women is the same as his taste in lawyers: only the very best with just the right amount of dirty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You want your criminal associate taken into police custody? We declare just enough so as to not arouse suspicion, so Walt’s one time winnings becomes seed money for an investment. If you’re committed enough, you can make any story work. I once told a woman I was Kevin Costner, and it worked because I believed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;this-is-an-h4&quot;&gt;this is an H4&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drum roll, please. Wait for it. Lazer tag. Lazer tag! 7,000 square feet of rollicking fun in the heart of northern Bernalillo County! It adds up perfectly. Walt’s a scientist, scientists love lazers. Plus, they got bumper boats, so…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>ubots.com.br/blog/badass/2015/08/08/because-i-say-so.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">ubots.com.br/blog/badass/2015/08/08/because-i-say-so.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Badass</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let's parse some CSS, deal with it.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve --watch&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;!--more--&gt; which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;code class=&quot;language-scss&quot;&gt;// Reset and dependencies
@import &quot;bootstrap/normalize&quot;;
@import &quot;bootstrap/print&quot;;
// @import &quot;bootstrap/glyphicons&quot;; desactivamos los glyphicons&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 00:51:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>ubots.com.br/blog/javascript/2015/08/07/lets-parse-some-css.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">ubots.com.br/blog/javascript/2015/08/07/lets-parse-some-css.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Javascript</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I am the one who knocks</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been waiting. I’ve been waiting all day. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Waiting&lt;/code&gt; for Gus to send one of his men to kill me. And it’s you. Who do you know, who’s okay with using children, Jesse? Who do you know… who’s allowed children to be murdered… hmm? Gus! He has, he has been ten steps ahead of me at every turn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;this-is-an-h2&quot;&gt;This is an H2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re his cook now. You’re the cook and you have proven that you can run a lab without me and now that cook has reason to kill me. Think about it! It’s brilliant. So go ahead. If you think that I am capable of doing this, then go ahead. Put a bullet, in my head, and kill me right now. DO IT! Do it. Do it. Do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Option A, you kill me right here and now. Apparently I’ve made that very easy for you. You can kill me, no witnesses and then spend the next few weeks or months tracking down Jesse Pinkman and you kill him too. A pointless exercise it seems to me but that is Option A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;this-is-an-h3&quot;&gt;this is an h3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I continue cooking, you and I both forget about &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WVR476WHmR8&quot;&gt;Pinkman&lt;/a&gt;. We forget this ever happened. We consider this a lone hiccup in an otherwise long and fruitful business arrangement. I prefer Option B.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’ll live. I asked to see you in order to… clear the air. There are uh, some… issues that could cause a misunderstanding between us and I think it’s in our best interest to lay the cards on the table. My brother-in-law, moments before he was attacked, someone called to warn him. I believe that same person was protecting me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;code class=&quot;language-scss&quot;&gt;%clearfix {
    &amp;amp;:after {
        content: '';
        display: block;
        clear: both;
    }
}&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those two men, the assassins. I believe I was their prime target, but that somehow they were steered away from me to my brother-in-law. Because of this ‘intervention’ I am alive. And yet, I think that this person was playing a much deeper game. He made that phone call because he wanted a shootout not a silent assassination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look, I’ll give you Jesse Pinkman, OK? Like you said, he’s the problem, he’s always been the problem and without him, we would… and he’s in town, alright? He’s not in Virginia or wherever the hell you’re looking for him. He’s right here in Albuquerque and I can take you to him, I’ll take you right to him. What do you say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;this-is-an-h4&quot;&gt;this is an H4&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s complicated and I don’t wish to discuss it. It’s none of your concern. You know what, let’s just say that I have a hell of a lot more on my mind, right now, than thinking about buying a damn car wash. Okay? So if you could just… please.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>ubots.com.br/blog/breaking/2015/08/07/i-am-the-one-who-knocks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">ubots.com.br/blog/breaking/2015/08/07/i-am-the-one-who-knocks.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Breaking</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The real secrets of CSS</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve --watch&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;code class=&quot;language-scss&quot;&gt;// Reset and dependencies
@import &quot;bootstrap/normalize&quot;;
@import &quot;bootstrap/print&quot;;
// @import &quot;bootstrap/glyphicons&quot;; desactivamos los glyphicons&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 23:04:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>ubots.com.br/blog/css/2015/08/06/the-real-secrets-of-css.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">ubots.com.br/blog/css/2015/08/06/the-real-secrets-of-css.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>css</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
